# **BEAU MASSIE**

918-839-4413



beauhmassie@gmail.com



Tulsa, OK



## **SUMMARY**

Experienced manager who led a team of greater than 10 direct reports. Possess six years of data experience in the chemical industry, combining a unique foundation in science with advanced programming skills. Certified in data analytics through the Google Data Analytics course, with a strong track record of delivering data-driven insights and process improvements.

### **EDUCATION**

Data Analyst

### University of Oklahoma

Bachelor's Degree in Chemistry 2017

additional course work completed: Deferential Equations, VBA programing

#### Carl Albert State College

Associates in Psychology and Pre-Engineering 2013

### SKILLS

- Management, Time and Project management
- Power BI, Tableau, Python, R, SQL
- VBA, API, CRUD, NoSQL, Excell
- Machine Learning, Hadoop, CSS, HTML, CSS, Statistics Modeling
- Leadership, Communication, Collaboration, Adaptability, Critical thinking, Initiative
- HPLC, ICP-MS, LC-MS, GC-MS, ISO 17025

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Google Data Analytics (Coursea, December 2022)
- Data Analytics Bootcamp (TCC expected graduation November 2024

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **Quality Chemist**

IChemtrade Logistics | 2021 - 2024

- Data Generation, Validation, transformation, and reporting
- Spear headed method and process development of HPIC
- Excell Automation to better quality of data and improve on efficiency of data validation
- · SOP writing

#### Lab Director

OKCTL | 2019 - 2021

- Data storage, validation, and reporting for over 100 clients in LIMS, custom COA generation, Excell
- Set up data processing and QC protocols
- Wrote ISO 17025 plan, and OSHA plan
- Started and managed six departments to address customer and state demands.

### **Process Production Technologist**

Umicore PMC | 2018 - 2019

- Wrote VBA program to automate batch creation
- Ran small scale process validation
- Worked with SAP